(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
重大告知あり！紫咲シオン Birthday アニソンライブ！！✨ #紫咲シオン生誕LIVE2024
Important announcement! Murasaki Shion Birthday Anime Song Live!! #MurasakiShionBirthdayLIVE2024
2024.12.08.
MURASAKI SHION
HAPPY BIRTHDAY
guest
戌神ころね 兎田ぺこら 宝鐘マリン
Inugami Korone, Usada Pekora, Houshou Marine
天音かなた 沙花叉クロヱ
Amane Kanata, Sakamata Chloe
がうる・ぐら こぼ・かなえる
Gawr Gura, Kobo Kanaeru
松本梨香
Matsumoto Rica
限界突破×サバイバー
作詞：森雪之丞 作曲：岩崎貴文
Genkai Toppa × Survivor
Lyrics: Mori Yukinojo, Composition: Iwasaki Takafumi
Go! Go! Go!
Survivor!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
興奮すっゾ！宇宙へ GO!
I'm so excited! Go to space!
最先端の “夢中” をどう！
How about the latest craze?
この手に 掴むよ
I'll grab it with these hands
素っ頓狂に笑ってタイ！
I want to laugh absurdly!
チンプンカンはなれっこダイ！
I'm used to things not making sense!
I can’t get no satisfaction.
退屈は 石になる
Boredom turns into stone
重くて落ちちゃう前に
Before it gets too heavy and falls
Let’s fly high
ワクワクの 羽根広げ
Spread your wings of excitement
次の世界へ行こう
Let's go to the next world
可能性のドアは 施錠されたまま
The door of possibility remains locked
やれやれ… 今度も 壁をブチ破る
Good grief... I'll break through the wall again
今だ！限界×突破 叫べ！ヘノヘノカッパ
Now! Break your limits, shout! Piece of cake!
無敵のオイラが そこで待っている
The invincible me is waiting there
ドラゴンボール超 全王様もオッタマゲ〜！！
Dragon Ball Super, even Zen-oh is stunned!!
Go! Go! Go!
限界突破×サバイバー
Genkai Toppa × Survivor
想像すっゾ！愉快な今日
Imagine it! A fun today!
天真☆爛漫☆機嫌は“上”
Innocent and cheerful, in high spirits!
夢見りゃ叶うよ 大混戦だ
If you dream it, it'll come true! It's a huge melee!
かかってこい！
Bring it on!
バッタンキューと捻ってポイ
Knock 'em flat, twist 'em and toss 'em away!
I can't get more satisfaction.
信じれば
If you believe...
WOO-HO
手の中に
...inside your hand...
渦巻くカメハメの波
...swirls the Kamehameha wave!
Let's make it
WOO-HO
寂しさを砕く時
When it's time to crush the sadness...
キミも戦士だろう
...you're a warrior too, right?
意外性を秘めたヤツが生き残る
Those who hide unexpected potential will survive!
マジかよ…
No way...
WOO-HO
100倍ヤバいサバイバル
A survival 100 times more dangerous!
行くぞ！限界×突破
Let's go! Breaking through the limits!
パワー全開！ヤッパ…
Full power! Just as expected...
WOO-HO
秒速進化のバトルが見せ場さ
...this battle of rapid evolution is the highlight!
ドラゴンボール超
Dragon Ball Super
破壊神だけへちゃむくれ
Even the Gods of Destruction are taken aback!
可能性のドアは施錠されたまま
The door of possibility remains locked.
ヤレヤレ…
Good grief...
WOO-HO
今度も壁をブチ破る
This time too, I'll smash through the wall!
今だ！限界×突破
Now! Breaking through the limits!
叫べ！へのへのカッパ
Shout it out! It's a piece of cake!
WOO-HO
無敵のオイラがそこで待っている
An invincible me is waiting there!
半端じゃない超
Not just half-baked Super,
超えてやるぜ超
I'll surpass even Super!
ドラゴンボール超
Dragon Ball Super
全王様もおったまげー！
Even the Omni-King will be shocked!
はい！というわけで1曲目は限界突破×サバイバー歌いました！
All right! And so, for the first song, I sang 'Genkai Toppa × Survivor'!
どう？かっこよかった？シオンの渾身のビーム！
How was it? Was it cool? Shion's full-power beam!
みんなちゃんと食らったかな？
Did everyone take the hit?
ってな感じで、誕生日を迎えましたー！
And with that, I've reached my birthday!
今日はですね、紫咲シオン・バースデーアニソンライブということで
Today, since it's the Murasaki Shion Birthday Anisong Live...
アニソンメインでガンガン歌っていくよ！
...I'm going to be singing lots of anime songs!
ハッシュタグはこちら！
Here is the hashtag!
#紫咲シオン生誕LIVE2024 でたくさんツイートしてくださいね！
Please tweet a lot using '#MurasakiShionBirthdayLIVE2024'!
いい声、お写真をたくさん後からシオンも見たいんで、あのいっぱいツイートしてくれると嬉しいです！
Shion wants to see lots of your comments and photos later, so I'd be happy if you tweeted a lot!
そして、なんとこのステージ！
And, check out this stage!
超かわいい！見て、めっちゃ良くない？
It's super cute! Look, isn't it great?
上にね、くまちゃんがいるの分かる？
Can you see there's a teddy bear on top?
お目目がね、きょきょろでね、超かわいいんですよ！めっちゃかわいい、本当に！
Its eyes are all sparkly and it's just so cute! Really, it's adorable!
素敵なステージに立たせていただいちゃいました！
I've been given the chance to stand on such a wonderful stage!
はい！というわけで、後半に重大告知もあるし！
All right! So, there's a major announcement in the second half too!
なんだろうね？楽しみだね。
I wonder what it is? Something to look forward to.
ライブ終わった後にも楽しみがあるので、最後まで絶対に見逃さないでください！
There's more to look forward to even after the live ends, so make sure not to miss anything until the very end!
まだまだいろんなアニソンを、いろんなゲストの方と一緒に歌っていくので
I'm going to be singing more anime songs with various guests...
一緒に楽しんでいこう！
...so let's have fun together!
それじゃあ次の曲、どうぞ！
Well then, here is the next song!
ロマンティックあげるよ
Romantikku Ageru yo
おいでファンタジー 好きさミステリー
Come here, fantasy! I love mystery!
君の若さを隠さないで
Don't hide your youth.
不思議したくて 冒険したくて
Wanting to wonder, wanting to adventure...
誰もみんなウズウズしてる
...everyone is itching to go.
大人のフリして あきらめちゃ
If you pretend to be an adult and give up...
奇跡の謎など 解けないよ
...you'll never solve the mystery of miracles!
もっとワイルドに
Be more wild!
もっとたくましく
Be more robust!
生きてごらん
Try living that way!
ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance.
ホントの勇気 見せてくれたら
If you show me true courage...
ロマンティックあげるよ
...I'll give you romance.
ロマンティックあげるよ　ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance, I'll give you romance
トキメク胸に
Into your throbbing heart
キラキラ光った 夢をあげるよ
I'll give you a sparkling dream
いつかワンダフル
Someday it'll be wonderful
きっとビューティフル
Surely it'll be beautiful
人のジャングル 迷い込んで
Straying into the human jungle
スリルしたくて
Wanting a thrill
幸せたくて
Wanting happiness
何故かみんな ソワソワしてる
For some reason, everyone is restless
思ったとおりに 叫ばなきゃ
You have to shout it out just as you thought
願いは空まで 届かない
Your wishes won't reach the sky
もっとセクシーに
More sexy
もっと美しく
More beautifully
生きてごらん
Try to live
ロマンティックあげるよ　ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance, I'll give you romance
ホントの涙 見せてくれたら
If you show me your true tears
ロマンティックあげるよ　ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance, I'll give you romance
淋しい心
A lonely heart
やさしく包んで 愛をあげるよ
I'll wrap it gently and give you love
ロマンティックあげるよ　ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance, I'll give you romance
ホントの勇気 見せてくれたら
If you show me your true courage
ロマンティックあげるよ　ロマンティックあげるよ
I'll give you romance, I'll give you romance
トキメク胸に
Into your throbbing heart
キラキラ光った 夢をあげるよ
I'll give you a sparkling dream
Together
作詞：D&Pプロジェクト　作曲：Rie
編曲：市川淳
Together
Lyrics: D&P Project / Composition: Rie
Arrangement: Jun Ichikawa
とっておき ふくつのこころ もって
With a special, indomitable heart
高いテンガン山 越えて行こう
Let's cross the high Mt. Coronet
誰をゲットかな？ どこで出会うかな？
Who will I catch? Where will we meet?
ワクワク気分 まるで秘密基地さ
This exciting feeling is just like a secret base
新しい町 僕らは進む
We move forward into new towns
輝く時の中で
Within the shining time
(イェイ イェイ イェイ イェイ!)
(Yay yay yay yay!)
甘くないさ バトルはいつだって
Battles are never easy
からい？苦い？渋い？すっぱいね？
Spicy? Bitter? Astringent? Sour, right?
生きてるんだ だから感じよう
We're alive, so let's feel it
一緒に (イェイ イェイ イェイ イェイ!)
Together (Yay yay yay yay!)
アクアジェットで 吹っ飛ばしてけ
Blow them away with Aqua Jet
モヤモヤ気分 霧払いして
Clearing away the gloomy feelings
ロッククライム 晴れ乗り越えたら
Once we overcome the Rock Climb and the sun shines
GOOD GOOD SMILE!! みんな
GOOD GOOD SMILE!! Everyone
GOOD GOOD SMILE!!
長い長い 旅の途中にいても
Even if we're in the middle of a long, long journey
数えきれぬ バトル思いだせば
If we remember the countless battles
時空を越えて 僕らは会える
Across space and time, we can meet
まぶしい みんなの顔
Everyone's dazzling faces
(イェイ イェイ イェイ イェイ!)
(Yay yay yay yay!)
まだまだ未熟 毎日が修行
Still inexperienced, every day is training
勝っても負けても 最後は握手さ
Win or lose, in the end we shake hands
なつきチェッカー ごめんねゼロ
Friendship Checker says zero, sorry
ホントに CRY CRY クライネ!!
It's really CRY CRY crying!!
きらめく瞳 ダイヤかパール
Sparkling eyes, Diamond or Pearl
まずは手始め
First, to start off...
クイックボール！！
Quick Ball!!
マルチバトルでばっちり決めたら
Once you've made a perfect move in a multi-battle
GOOD GOOD SMILE!!
もっと
More
GOOD GOOD SMILE!!
過去と未来
Past and future
僕らはめざす
We aim for
誓ったあの場所へ
To that place we promised
イェイイェイイェイイェイ イェ！！
Yay yay yay yay Yay!!
甘くないさ バトルはいつだって
It's not sweet, battles are always
からい？にがい？しぶい？すっぱいね？
Spicy? Bitter? Astringent? Sour, isn't it?
生きてるんだ だから感じよう
We're alive, so let's feel it
いっしょに
Together
イェイイェイイェイイェイ イェ！！
Yay yay yay yay Yay!!
アクアジェットで ぶっ飛ばしてけ
Blow them away with Aqua Jet
モヤモヤ気分 霧払いして
Mist-clear that foggy feeling
ロッククライム ほら乗り越えたら
Rock Climb, see, once you've overcome it
GOOD GOOD SMILE!!
みんな
Everyone
GOOD GOOD SMILE!!
ねぇ、君たちの夢って何かな？
Hey, what's your dream?
ポケモン151匹ゲット！
To catch all 151 Pokémon!
あら、私と同じ！
Oh, same as me!
え～？おとなのくせにへんなの～
Eh~? That's weird for an adult~
なによ～ いけない？
What~? Is that bad?
いけなくないけどさ...
It's not bad, but...
ねえ君たちさ、ほかにはどんなユメがあるの？
Hey guys, what other dreams do you have?
う～んとねぇ...
Umm, well...
もうひとつのゆめはねぇ...
My other dream is...
はやくおとなになりたいんだ
I want to become an adult soon
えっ、どうして？
Eh, why?
はやくおとなになりたいの
I want to become an adult soon
こどもって楽しいじゃない
Being a child is fun, isn't it?
でもね、なんだかなってみたい
But, I somehow want to try becoming one
じゃあこんどはわたしのユメ、いうわね...
Then, I'll tell you my dream this time...
もういちどこどもにもどってみたい
I want to try being a child once more
え～？なんで～？
Eh~? Why~?
もういちどこどもにもどってみたいの
I want to try being a child once more
おとなでいいのに
Being an adult is fine, though
いちにちだけでもなれないかな
I wish I could be one for just a day
なれっこないよ～
There's no way you can~
んもう、いじわるぅ
Oh, you're so mean!
むかしわたしが まだこどもだったころ
A long time ago, when I was still a child
ポケットにいれてた たくさんのたからもの
The many treasures I used to keep in my pocket
いまでもときどき かおをのぞかせるのよ
Even now, they occasionally peek out
それってもしかして ピカチュウ？
Could that be... Pikachu?
さあ、なんでしょうね？
Well, I wonder what it is?
むかしのこども いまのこども
Children of the past, children of now
ポケットのなかみは いつだって
The contents of their pockets are always
おとこのこでも おんなのこでも
Whether it's a boy or a girl
ポケットのなかみは だれだって ファンタジー
Everyone's pocket is full of fantasy
もしもおとなになったなら
If I ever become an adult
なにしてみたい？
What would you want to do?
こどもとあそんであげるんだ
I'd play with the children
やっぱりあそびたいんだ
You just want to play after all
でもね、しごともちょっとするよ
But, I'll do a bit of work too
あのね、わたしがもしもね...
You know, if I could...
もういちどこどもにもどれたなら
If I could return to being a child once more
なにしてみたいの？
What would you want to do?
あってみたいひとがいるの
There's someone I want to see
え～、だれなの～？
Eh~, who is it~?
いちにちだけでもあえないかな
I wonder if I could see them for just a day
あ！はつこいのひとだ！
Ah! It's your first crush!
あったり～！
Spot on!
むかしわたしが いつかであうはずの
A long time ago, for someone I was meant to meet
ポケットにいれてた てづくりのプレゼント
A handmade present I kept in my pocket
いまでもときどき かおがあかくなるのよ
Even now, my face occasionally turns red
プレゼントわたせなかったの？
You couldn't give them the present?
さあ、どうだったかしら？
Well, I wonder how it went?
むかしのこども いまのこども
Children of the past, children of now
ポケットのなかみは いつだって
The contents of their pockets are always
おとこのこでも おんなのこでも
Whether it's a boy or a girl
ポケットのなかみは だれだって...
The contents of everyone's pockets are...
ポケットの　なかみは　だれだって　ファンタジー
Everyone's pocket is filled with fantasy
おーい！
Hey!
もしもし？
Hello?
んん……。んんん……。
Mmm... mmm...
あれ？ ここは……
Huh? This place is...
……って、え！
...Wait, what?!
あ、あなたは……
Ah, you are...
あ、こんにちは。
Ah, hello.
さっそくフレンドリー松本梨香です！
It's the ever-friendly Rica Matsumoto!
梨香さんがなんで目の前に？
Why is Rica-san in front of me?
て、ここどこ？
Wait, where am I?
え、ここは……
Eh, this is...
……シオンちゃんの夢の中です。
...inside Shion-chan's dream.
へ！ 私が梨香さんに会いたくて……
Eh! So I wanted to meet Rica-san so much...
……その願いが夢になって実現したってこと？
...that the wish became a dream and came true?
やった！ ずっと会いたかったです！
Yay! I've always wanted to meet you!
あぁ、嬉しいな、そんな風に言ってくれて。
Ah, I'm so happy to hear you say that.
やばい、今夢が叶ってる。
Oh my god, my dream is coming true right now.
実は、私の人生の初恋が……
Actually, the first love of my life...
……梨香さんの演じているキャラクターでして。
...was a character played by Rica-san.
あの、好きです！
Um, I love you!
すごい「好きです」なんて気持ちを伝えてくれて……
Thank you so much for telling me how you feel,
……どうもありがとう。とっても嬉しいです。
like "I love you." I'm very happy.
言っちゃった……
I said it...
え、今、めちゃあつです。
Uh, right now, I'm so flustered.
落ち着いて、落ち着いて。
Calm down, calm down.
なんかお手洗い行きたいみたいになってる。大丈夫？
You look like you need the bathroom. Are you okay?
ちょっとあの、一つお願いがありまして。
Um, I have one request.
はい、何でしょう？
Yes, what is it?
もしよかったらなんですけど……
If it's alright with you...
……私、誕生日を迎えまして……
...I've just had my birthday...
え、おめでとう！
Eh, congratulations!
お祝いの言葉をいただけると……
If I could get a birthday message...
もちろんです。行きますよ、じゃ。
Of course. Here I go then.
シオン、お誕生日おめでとう！
Shion, happy birthday!
わぁ、ありがとうございます！
Wow, thank you so much!
もう、この一生に悔いはないです。
I have no regrets in my life anymore.
ありがとうございます！ ほんとに、ほんとに。
Thank you! Truly, truly.
ね、ほんとにこちらこそありがとう。
Hey, thank you as well.
このあともあるし、ちょっと落ち着きます。
There's more to come, so I'll try to calm down.
梨香さん！ はい？
Rica-san! Yes?
もしよかったら私と一緒に……
If you'd like, would you...
……歌を歌ってくれませんか？
...sing a song with me?
もちろんです！
Of course!
ありがとうございます！ 緊張する……
Thank you so much! I'm nervous...
それでは、聞いてください。
Now then, please listen.
ハイタッチ！
High Touch!
どうぞ！
Please enjoy!
けんか なかなおり またけんか
Fight, make up, and fight again
言いたいこと いっぱいあるけど
There's so much I want to say, but...
いちばんは……
The most important thing is...
「いてくれてありがとう！」
"Thank you for being here!"
旅はみちづれ 世はなさけ
A journey needs a companion, life needs kindness
わかったような 顔してるけど
Even though I look like I understand...
ほんとうは……
...the truth is...
「いてくれてうれしい！」
"I'm happy you're here!"
ナイスパートナー！
Nice partner!
ナイスライバル！
Nice rival!
おしてあげるよ
I'll give you a push
ひっぱってあげる
I'll pull you along
見上げる太陽 なんだか
Looking up at the sun, somehow...
まぶしくて
...it's so bright
うまくいったら ハイタッチ！
If things go well, high touch!
へこんじゃっても もとどおり！
Even if we feel down, we'll bounce back!
いっしょ ならば……
As long as we're together...
あきらめるのははやいぜ GO GO GO!
It's too early to give up, GO GO GO!
ねらいさだめ バブルこうせん
Take aim, Bubble Beam
たよりになる ポッチャマだけど
Piplup is so reliable, but...
ときどきは……
Sometimes...
はずれちゃって めっちゃピンチ！
...it misses and we're in a real pinch!
きあいこめて 10まんボルト
Putting my spirit into Thunderbolt
おれのじまん ピカチュウだけど
Pikachu is my pride and joy, but...
かんたんに……
It's not...
勝てるわけじゃない！
...always easy to win!
ナイスパートナー！
Nice partner!
ナイスライバル！
Nice rival!
声かけあって
Calling out to each other
フォローしあえば
And following up for each other
おもったとおりに わざも
The moves will land just as intended
決まる！
They'll land!
決まりだす...
Starting to decide...
うまくいったらハイタッチ！
If it goes well, high-five!
きょうの勝利は忘れない！
I won't forget today's victory!
いっしょならば...
If we're together...
どんなピンチも逃げてく
Any pinch will run away
腕を伸ばしハイタッチ！
Stretch out your arm and high-five!
笑顔いっぱいこころづよい！
Full of smiles and feeling strong!
いっしょならば...
If we're together...
つよいあいてもウェルカム！
Even a strong opponent is welcome!
GO GO GO!
きょうもあしたもあさっても
Today, tomorrow, and the day after
旅はずっとつづいていくけど
The journey continues on and on, but...
いつだって... すぐそばにその笑顔！
Always... that smile is right there!
きたへみなみへにしひがし
North, south, west, east
景色くるくる変わるけど
The scenery changes around and around, but...
どこにいたって... いつもその笑顔！
Wherever you are... that smile is always there!
ナイスパートナー！ ナイスライバル！
Nice partner! Nice rival!
まもってくれるよ たすけてくれる
You protect me, you help me
ひろがる荒野に道が
In the spreading wasteland, the path
まっすぐに
goes straight ahead
空のしたでハイタッチ！
High-five under the sky!
ことばよりもわかりやすい
Easier to understand than words
いっしょならば...
If we're together...
夢にむかってとべるぜ！
We can fly toward our dreams!
うまくいったらハイタッチ！
If it goes well, high-five!
へこんじゃってももとどおり！
Even if we're feeling down, we'll be back to normal!
いっしょならば...
If we're together...
あきらめるのは早いぜ！
It's too early to give up!
GO GO GO!
うまくいったねハイタッチ！
It went well, high-five!
バトルあいてとハンドシェイク！
Handshake with the battle opponent!
いっしょならば...
If we're together...
もっと遠くにいけるぜ！
We can go even further!
GO GO GO!
というわけで、梨香さんとデュエットさせていただきました、「ハイタッチ！」でした！
So, I got to perform a duet with Rica-san. That was "Hi-Touch!"
イェーイ！
Yay!
楽しかったね。
That was fun.
楽しかったです。梨香さんの歌声、隣で聴けて本当に幸せでした。
It was fun. I'm so happy I got to hear your voice right next to me.
それは良かったです。シオンちゃんも、とっても可愛かったです。
I'm glad. Shion-chan was very cute too.
ありがとうございます！嬉しい。
Thank you! I'm so happy.
改めて、お誕生日おめでとうございます。
Once again, happy birthday.
こちらこそ、今日はありがとうございました。
Thank you so much for today.
あ、やばい。そろそろライブ会場の私が目覚めそうです。
Oh no. It seems the "me" at the live venue is about to wake up.
まだ梨香さんと話してたいのに！
I still want to talk with Rica-san!
この後のライブも、めちゃめちゃ頑張ってください。
Good luck with the rest of the live performance.
ありがとうございます、梨香さん。本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you, Rica-san. Thank you so much!
こちらこそありがとうございました。
Thank you as well.
では、ライブ頑張ってきます！ありがとうございました！
Well then, I'll go give it my all for the live! Thank you!
応援してるよ！
I'm rooting for you!
はい！
Yes!
シルエット
Silhouette
作詞・作曲：谷口鮪
Lyrics & Composition: Maguro Taniguchi
いっせーのーせで踏み込むゴーライン
With a "one-two-three," we step across the goal line
僕らは何も 何も まだ知らぬ
We don't know anything, anything yet
一線越えて振り返るともうない
Once we cross the line, there's no looking back
僕らは何も 何も まだ知らぬ
We don't know anything, anything yet
うだって うだって うだってく
Sweltering, sweltering, we're sweltering away
煌めく汗がこぼれるのさ
Glistening sweat starts to fall
覚えてないことも たくさんあっただろう
There were probably many things we don't remember
誰も彼もシルエット
Everyone, everything is a silhouette
大事にしてたもの 忘れたフリをしたんだよ
We pretended to forget the things we held dear
なにもない なによ 笑えるさ
There's nothing, what's there? It's laughable
いっせーのーで思い出す少年
With a "one-two-three," the boy remembers
僕らは何もかもを欲しがった
We wanted everything
わかってるって あぁ気づいてるって
I understand, ah, I've noticed
時計の針は　日々は止まらない
The hands of the clock, the days don't stop
奪って奪っていく
Stealing away, stealing away
流れる時と記憶
Flowing time and memories
遠く遠く遠くなって
Getting further and further away
覚えてないことも　たくさんあっただろう
There must have been many things I don't remember
誰も彼もシルエット　恐れて止まらぬこと
Everyone's a silhouette, fearing things that won't stop
知らないフリをしたんだよ
I pretended not to know
なにもない　笑えるさ
There's nothing, I can laugh about it
ひらりとひらりと舞ってる　この葉の様に揺れることなく
Fluttering, fluttering, without swaying like these leaves
焦燥もなく過ごしていたいよ
I want to spend my days without impatience
覚えてないことも　たくさんあったけど
There were many things I didn't remember
きっとずっと変わらない　ものがあることを
But I'm sure there's something that will never change
教えてくれたあなたは　消える消えるシルエット
You, who taught me that, are a disappearing silhouette
大事にしたいもの持って大人になるんだ
I'll become an adult holding onto things I want to cherish
どんな時も離さずに　守り続けよう
Without ever letting go, I'll keep protecting them
そしたらいつの日にか　なにもかもを笑えるさ
Then, one day, I'll be able to laugh at everything
ひらりとひらりと舞ってる　木の葉が飛んでゆく
Fluttering, fluttering, the leaves fly away
不思議だね　いまの気持ち
It's strange, the way I feel right now
空から降ってきたみたい
It feels like it fell from the sky
特別な季節の色が
The colors of this special season
ときめきを見せるよ
Show me this heart-pounding feeling
初めて出会った時から
Since the first time we met
予感に騒ぐ心のメロディ
The melody in my heart stirs with a premonition
とめられないとまらない　な・ぜ
I can't stop it, it won't stop, why?
届けて　切なさには
Deliver it, to this heartache
名前をつけようか “Snow halation”
Shall we give it a name? 'Snow halation'
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap
待てずに悔しいけど好きって純情
I can't wait, it's frustrating, but 'I love you' is pure
微熱の中　ためらってもダメだね
In this slight fever, it's no use hesitating
飛び込む勇気に賛成
I'm all for the courage to dive in
まもなく Start!!
It's starting soon!!
音もなく気配もなく
Soundlessly, without a sign
静かに運命は変わる
Destiny changes quietly
これからの未来に胸の
In the future to come, my heart's...
鼓動が早くなる
...beat speeds up
例えば困った時には
For example, when you're in trouble
すぐ駆けつけて抱きしめたくて
I want to rush over and hold you tight
どこにいてもどこでも Fly high
Wherever I am, anywhere, Fly high
急いで　いつの間にか
Hurry, before I knew it
大きくなりすぎた “True emotion”
This 'True emotion' has grown too big
夢だけ見てる様じゃ つらいよ
Just dreaming is painful.
恋人は君って言いたい
I want to say you are my lover.
優しい目が
Your kind eyes...
とまどってるイヤだよ
...are bewildered, I hate it.
このまま一気に愛情
All at once, my affection...
あずけて Please!!
...give it to me, Please!!
届けて 切なさには名前をつけようか
Deliver it. Shall we name this heartache?
“Snow halation”
想いが重なるまで
Until our feelings overlap.
待てずに悔しいけど
I can't wait, it's frustrating but...
好きって純情
...my love is pure heart.
微熱の中
In the slight fever...
ためらってもダメだね
...hesitating is no good.
飛び込む勇気に賛成
I agree with the courage to dive in.
まもなく Start!!
Very soon, Start!!
ONE PUNCH!
3, 2, 1 Kill shot!
参上！ 必勝！ 至上最強！！
Arrived! Certain victory! The strongest ever!!
なんだってんだ？ フラストレーション
What is it? Frustration.
俺は止まらない
I won't stop.
ONE PUNCH! 完了！ 連戦連勝！
ONE PUNCH! Completed! Consecutive victories!
俺は喝！ 常に勝つ！！ 圧勝！
I'm a shout! Always win!! A complete victory!
Power! Get power!
Get power! ギリギリ
Get power! At the limit...
限界まで
...to the limit.
HERO
俺を讃える声や
Voices praising me...
喝采なんて欲しくはないさ
...I don't want any applause.
HERO
だから人知れず悪と闘う
So I fight evil in secret.
Nobody knows who he is.
天覆い
The sky covered...
押し寄せる敵
...enemies surging.
俺は背を向けはしない
I will not turn my back.
HERO
ならば揺るぎなき覚悟したため
Then, having prepared an unwavering resolve...
繰り出せ鉄拳
...unleash the iron fist.
3, 2, 1 Fight back!
参上！ Go on! 正々堂々！！
Arrived! Go on! Fair and square!!
どうなってんだ？ 何も感じねぇ
What's happening? I don't feel anything.
もはや敵居ねぇ！
There are no more enemies!
JUSTICE! 執行！ 問答無用！
JUSTICE! Execution! No questions asked!
俺が断つ！ 悪を断つ！ 合掌！
I'll cut! Cut off evil! Prayer!
Power! Get power!
Get power! アドレナリン
Get power! Adrenaline...
溢れ出すぜ！
...it's overflowing!
Power! Get power!
鍛えた技をぶちかませ！
Blast them with your trained skills!
HERO
どんなに強い奴も
No matter how strong they are...
ちっぽけなガキだったんだ
...they were just small kids.
HERO
弱き己乗り越え強くなる
Overcoming your weak self and becoming stronger.
Nobody knows who he is.
神宿る拳掲げて
Raise the fist where a god dwells...
俺は突き進むだけさ
...I'll just keep moving forward.
HERO
いつか敗北に汚泥なめるまで
Until one day I taste the mud of defeat...
闘うHERO
...the fighting HERO.
俺は諦めない
I won't give up.
その胸に未来を描き
Drawing the future in that chest...
目覚め行く世界へ今
...now to the awakening world.
舞い上がれ 強く高く
Soar high, strong and high.
どんな時でも なにがあっても
No matter when, no matter what happens.
だから人知れず悪と闘う
So, I fight against evil in secret
Nobody knows
神宿る拳掲げて 俺は
Raising my fist where a god dwells, I...
突き進むだけさ HERO
...will only push forward, a HERO
いつか敗北に汚泥なめるまで
Until the day I taste the mud of defeat
闘う HERO
A fighting HERO
孤独な HERO
A lonely HERO
I wanna be a 最強 HERO
I wanna be the strongest HERO
This game
回り続ける
I won't let myself become a cog
歯車には成り下がらない
that just keeps on turning
平均演じる
Acting average,
誕生から始まった地獄
a hell that started from birth
遊び半分で
A world on a board led by a god
神が導いた盤上の世界
as if for fun
no no no game no life
ぬるい平穏をばっさり切り捨てて
Cutting off lukewarm peace, I'll carve
栄光への階段に存在刻むんだ
my existence into the stairs to glory
目に映るのは完全勝利の運命
What's reflected in my eyes is the fate of total victory
何もかも計算通り
Everything is exactly as calculated
変えてやる染まらない空白で
I'll change it with an untainted blank space
We are maverick
救済なんていらない
We don't need salvation
どんな理不尽襲おうとも
No matter what absurdity attacks,
勝てばいいだけの話だろ
it's just a matter of winning, right?
駆け引きと才能が
Tactics and talent
無敗誘う
invite invincibility
生まれ直した
I'll enjoy it
命で楽しむさ
with this reborn life
自分だけは
I'm the only one
自分信じてる
who believes in myself
心に潜む
There's no opponent stronger
闇より強い相手はいない
than the darkness lurking in the heart
挫けぬ限り
As long as you don't break,
そこに敗北はあり得ない
defeat is impossible there
上辺の個性で安心と引き換えに
Don't kill your pride in exchange for peace
プライド殺すな no no no sense
with superficial individuality, no no no sense
of life
野蛮な雑音を引っ張り蹴飛ばして
Dragging and kicking away the barbaric noise,
誰より純粋な声上げるんだ
raising a voice purer than anyone's
戦うことはきっと間違いじゃない
Fighting is surely not a mistake
手応えが教えてくれた
The feeling in my hands told me
全て失っても勝ち残れ
Even if you lose everything, survive and win
We are maverick
常識なんていらない
We don't need common sense
前へならえ向かう先に
Following the leader, what's waiting ahead
待ってるのは退屈だろ
is just boredom, right?
言いなりじゃつまらない
Just doing as told is boring,
挑んでやる
I'll challenge it
生まれ直した
Making even this reborn life
命も駒にして
a game piece
自分だけの道を
Following my own path
最後まで
until the very end
迷わない
An unhesitating
選ばれし者 真っ赤なうぬぼれでも
chosen one, even with a bright red conceit
誇らしく生き抜くための
Because I only know one way
方法を一つしか知らないから
to live proudly
We are maverick
救済なんていらない
We don't need salvation
どんな理不尽襲おうとも
No matter what absurdity attacks,
勝てばいいだけの話だろ
it's just a matter of winning, right?
駆け引きと才能が
Tactics and talent
無敗誘う
invite invincibility
生まれ直した命で
With this reborn life...
...分した火の池で
...at the lake of fire divided by minutes.
楽しむさ
I'll enjoy it.
この世界手にして笑うんだ
I'll take this world in my hands and laugh.
We are maverick
最強の maverick gamers
The strongest maverick gamers.
空白ならば何者にもなれる
If it's a blank space, we can become anyone.
自分だけは自分信じてる
Only I believe in myself.
名前のない怪物
Namae no Nai Kaibutsu (Monster Without a Name)
御伽話は
It seems the fairy tale
さっき死んだみたい
died just now.
煉瓦の病棟で
In the brick ward,
うまく歌えなくて
I couldn't sing well.
霧に煙る夜
On a night misty with fog,
浮かべ赤い月
a red moon floats.
ほらみて私を
Look at me,
目を逸らさないで
don't look away.
黒い鉄格子の中で私は生まれてきたんだ
I was born inside black iron bars.
悪意の代償を願え望むがままにお前に
Wish for the price of malice, just as you desire.
さあ与えよう正義を 壊して壊される前に
Now, let me give you justice, before I break and am broken.
因果の代償を払い共に行こう名前のない怪物
Pay the price of causality and let's go together, nameless monster.
耳鳴りがしてる
My ears are ringing.
鉄条網うるさくって
The barbed wire is so loud.
思い出せないの
I can't remember
あの日の旋律
that day's melody.
雨はまだ止まない
The rain hasn't stopped yet.
何にも見えないの
I can't see anything.
ほらみてこんなに
Look, I've grown
大きくなったの
this much.
黒い雨降らせこの空 私は望まれないもの
Let black rain fall from this sky. I am something unwanted.
ひび割れたノイローゼ愛す同罪の傍観者たちに
To the cracked neurosis and the loving, equally guilty bystanders.
さあ今ふるえ正義を 消せない傷を抱きしめて
Now, wield justice. Embracing the indelible wounds.
この身体を受け入れ共に行こう名前のない怪物
Accept this body and let's go together, nameless monster.
ああ神ハ告ゲル
Ah, God declares...
真ノ世界ヲ
...the true world.
名前のない怪物
Monster Without a Name
黒い雨 降らせ この空
Make black rain fall from this sky
私は 望まれないもの
I am something unwanted
ひび割れた ノイローゼ
A cracked neurosis
愛す 同罪の 傍観者達に
To the guilty bystanders I love
さあ今 ふるえ 正義を
Now, tremble with justice
消せない 傷を 抱きしめて
Embracing these indelible wounds
この 身体を 受け入れ
Accepting this body
共に 行こう 名前のない 怪物
Let's go together, monster without a name
教えて 教えてよ その仕組みを
Tell me, tell me, how it works
僕の中に 誰がいるの?
Who is inside of me?
壊れた 壊れたよ この世界で
It's broken, it's broken, in this world
君が笑う 何も見えずに
You're laughing, without seeing a thing
unravel
作詞・作曲: TK
Lyrics/Composition: TK
壊れた 僕なんてさ 息を止めて
Someone broken like me, stops breathing
ほどけない もう ほどけないよ 真実さえ
Unraveling, no longer unraveling, even the truth
freeze
壊せる 壊せない 狂える 狂えない
Can break, can't break, can go mad, can't go mad
あなたを見つけて 揺れた
I found you and shook
歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は
In this distorted world, I'm gradually
透き通って見えなくなって
becoming transparent and invisible
見つけないで 僕のことを 見つめないで
Don't find me, don't look at me
誰かが描いた世界の中で あなたを傷つけたくはないよ
In a world someone else drew, I don't want to hurt you
覚えていて 僕のことを 鮮やかなまま
Remember me, just as vivid as I am
無限に広がる孤独が絡まる
Infinite loneliness intertwines
無邪気に笑った記憶が刺さって
The memory of innocently laughing stabs at me
動けない 動けない 動けない 動けない 動けない 動けないよ
Can't move, can't move, can't move, can't move, can't move, can't move!
unravelling the world
変わってしまった 変えられなかった
It's changed, it couldn't be changed
2つが絡まる 2人が滅びる
The two intertwine, the two perish
壊せる 壊せない 狂える 狂えない
Can break, can't break, can go mad, can't go mad
あなたを汚せないよ 揺れた
I can't defile you, I shook
歪んだ世界にだんだん僕は
In this distorted world, I'm gradually
透き通って見えなくなって
becoming transparent and invisible
見つけないで 僕のことを 見つめないで
Don't find me, don't look at me
誰かが仕組んだ孤独な罠に
In this lonely trap someone set
未来がほどけてしまう前に
before the future unravels
思い出して 僕のことを 鮮やかなまま
Remember me, just as vivid as I am
忘れないで 忘れないで 忘れないで 忘れないで
Don't forget me, don't forget me, don't forget me, don't forget me
変わってしまったことに paralyze
Paralyzed by the fact that things have changed
変えられないことだらけの paradise
A paradise full of things that can't be changed
覚えていて 僕のことを
Remember me
教えて
Tell me
僕の中に 誰がいるの?
Who is inside of me?
はい、みんなここまで楽しんでみてもらえましたか？
Hi, everyone! Have you been enjoying the show so far?
そしてなんと気づいた時にはもう...
And what do you know, before I realized it...
ホロウィッチの衣装にお着替えしてました！
I've already changed into my Holowitch outfit!
どうでしょうか？
What do you think?
おさらに、いや元々可愛いのにさらに可愛くなったというか...
It's even... no, I was already cute but I've become even cuter...
可愛さは変わらないままというか、素敵な衣装ですね！
or rather, my cuteness remains the same, it's a lovely outfit, isn't it?
はい！さてさてみんな、最初に話した重大告知...
Alright! So, everyone, about the major announcement...
覚えてる？気になってたよね、ちゃんと今までずっとね。
Do you remember the one I talked about earlier? You've been curious all this time, haven't you?
いやでも、うーん...言おうかな...
Well, but, hmm... should I say it...?
いややめとこうかな...
Maybe I should hold off...
いやどうしようかな...
Hmm, what should I do...?
やめとこうかな！
Maybe I'll pass!
はい！というわけで、じゃあ今日はここまで！
Okay! So, that's it for today!
ライブ終わり！ありがとうみんな見てくれて！
The live is over! Thanks everyone for watching!
重大告知あり！！
Murasaki Shion Birthday アニソンライブ！！
Major Announcement!!
Murasaki Shion Birthday Anisong Live!!
いやいやいや待って待って待って待って！
No, no, no, wait, wait, wait, wait!
なんと、紫咲シオン、新しいオリジナル曲が出ます！イェーイ！
Actually, Murasaki Shion is releasing a new original song! Yay!
※現在のリリース情報は収録時点のものになります
各種音楽配信サイトでは12月8日0時より配信開始されております
*Current release info is as of the time of recording.
Release began on various music streaming sites from Dec 8th at 0:00.
今回ですね、初めてのアニメーションMVとなっていて、
This time, it's my first ever animated music video,
このあとライブ後にプレミアム公開されます！
and it'll have a premiere right after this live!
さらに、本日の24時、各種音楽配信サイトにてリリースされます！
Furthermore, it'll be released on various music streaming platforms at midnight tonight!
プレミアム公開のあとはメンバー限定でミニライブもあるのでよかったら見てください！
After the premiere, there's also a member-only mini-live, so please check it out if you'd like!
メンバー入ってる方もね、入ってない方もこれを機にちょっと見ていただけたらなと思っております。
Whether you're already a member or not, I hope you'll take this opportunity to take a look.
どうでしょうか？はい！
How does that sound? Okay!
はい！というわけで曲の後にはあの告知もあるのでお楽しみに！
Alright! So after the song, there's also *that* announcement, so please look forward to it!
最後の曲はさっき言ったオリ曲を初披露です！
The last song is the first performance of the original song I mentioned!
ピノキオピーさんに書き下ろしていただきました！
It was written specifically for me by PinocchioP!
曲名は「ごめんねメディスン」です！
The song title is "Gomen ne Medicine"!
ごめんねメディスン
作詞・作曲・編曲：ピノキオピー
Sorry Medicine
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: PinocchioP
変身できる 変身できちゃうから
I can transform, I can really transform
今日も生意気に笑ってる
So I'm wearing a cheeky smile again today
調合してる 調合していたのは
I'm compounding, what I was compounding was...
君を癒せる薬
A medicine to heal you
この薬草はちょっと苦いから やめとこうを繰り返して
This herb is a bit bitter, so I'll skip it, repeating that
このキノコはなんかヤバいけど まあいっか後悔して
This mushroom is kind of dangerous, but oh well, and I regret it
ちょっと擦りむいた傷 隠したセンシティブ なんでもないよ
Hiding a slightly scraped wound, sensitive, it's nothing
無限にあるけど
It's infinite, but...
めちゃ伝えたい 伝えたい 伝えたいんだ 好きを
I really want to tell you, tell you, tell you that I like you
でも言えない 言えない 言えないや はずいも
But I can't say it, say it, say it, it's embarrassing too
君を想って作った薬が
The medicine I made while thinking of you
毒になったら ごめんねメディスン
If it becomes poison, sorry medicine
イェーイ！ごめんねメディスン
Yeah! Sorry medicine
ちゃんとありがとうが言えなくて
I couldn't properly say thank you
届け 届け 君に
Reach you, reach you
わたしのメディスン
My medicine
ごめんねメディスン
Sorry medicine
あ、あったらこうなっちゃうな そうなったらしょうがないな
If it happens, it happens, if it's like that, it can't be helped
予想外の副作用 ガツンと食らっちゃうわ
An unexpected side effect, it'll hit you hard
イメージ イメージ イメージ イメージ 君の笑顔 アメージング
Image, image, image, image, your amazing smile
でも涙が混ざっちゃ パーセンテージ
But tears mixed in, percentage
用法とはちょっと違うから ちゃんとしようと思ったり
It's a bit different from the instructions, so I thought I should be careful
用量がわかんなくなっても なんとかなれと祈ったり
Even if I don't know the dosage, I prayed it would work out somehow
ハッと気がついたんです 飛んでった浮遊気分 どうでもいいよ
Suddenly I realized, I'm in a floating mood, doesn't matter
すごい気になるけど
It bothers me a lot, but...
魔法 唱えたい 唱えたい 唱えたいんだ 熱いの
I want to chant, chant, chant a spell, it's hot
でも冷たい 温度は怖いよ
But the cold temperature is scary
ノリで作ったファジーな薬が
The fuzzy medicine I made on a whim...
合わなかったら ごめんねメディスン
If it didn't suit you, sorry medicine
イェーイ！ごめんねメディスン
Yeah! Sorry medicine
冗談で誤魔化してばかりで
Just covering it up with jokes
後悔して 後悔して もう一度
Regret it, regret it, once more
めちゃ伝えたい 伝えたい 伝えたいんだ 好きを
I really want to tell you, tell you, tell you that I like you
でも言えない 言えない 言えないや はずいも
But I can't say it, say it, say it, it's embarrassing too
君を想って作った薬が
The medicine I made while thinking of you
毒になったら ごめんねメディスン
If it becomes poison, sorry medicine
イェーイ！ごめんねメディスン
Yeah! Sorry medicine
ちゃんとありがとうが言えなくて
I couldn't properly say thank you
届け 届け
Reach you, reach you
君に わたしのメディスン
To you, my medicine
不器用なメディスン
Clumsy medicine
素直になれなくって
Unable to be honest
ごめんねメディスン
Sorry medicine
いつもありがとうって
Saying thank you as always
ずっと一緒にいようって
Let's be together forever
ちゃんと言えなくって
Unable to say it properly
溶けちゃったメディスン
The medicine melted away
ごめんねメディスン
Sorry medicine
ちゃんと届いてる？
Is it reaching you properly?
みんな、紫咲シオンバースデーアニソンライブ、最後まで見てくれてありがとう！
Everyone, thank you for watching my Birthday Anisong Live until the very end!
最後に、誕生日記念グッズのお知らせです。
Finally, I have an announcement regarding my birthday merchandise.
紫咲シオン誕生日記念グッズ2024が出ます！
Murasaki Shion's 2024 Birthday Merchandise is coming out!
もうすでにね、今出ちゃってるイラストが可愛すぎるよね。
The illustration already on screen right now is just too cute, isn't it?
それでは、一個ずつ見ていきましょう！
Now, let's take a look at them one by one!
まずは、こちら。キャンバスアート！
First off is this: the Canvas Art!
初めて出すよね、キャンバスアート。イラストは、りいちゅ先生に描いてもらいました。
It's the first time I'm releasing canvas art. Riichu-sensei drew this illustration.
現代のキラキラ魔法少女がテーマのキービジュアルです。
The theme of this key visual is a modern, sparkling magical girl.
めっちゃ可愛いし、さすがに世界救ってそうだよね。
It's so cute, she looks like she'd definitely save the world.
しおっこもいて可愛いね。
Shiokko is there too, which is adorable.
ぜひね、お手にとって、ちゃんと見ていただきたいですね、この素敵なイラストを。
I really want you all to get your hands on this and take a good look at this wonderful illustration.
そしてお次は、こちら。マルチケース！
And next is this: the Multi-case!
イラストは、夢ノ内先生に描いてもらいました。
The illustration was drawn by Yumenouchi-sensei.
いや、これもね、可愛すぎる。ゲーミング衣装のシオンとなってます。
Wow, this is also too cute. It features Shion in her gaming outfit.
え、なんとね、ついてるラバーパーツ、このキーホルダーみたいなやつがね、取り外し可能で、別々でも使えちゃうんですね。
And surprisingly, the rubber part—this keychain-like thing—is detachable, so you can use them separately.
一緒につけるも良し、別のアイテムと合わせても良しな可愛すぎるアイテム。
It's a super cute item that looks great whether attached or paired with other things.
クリアになってるから、入れてるものが見えて、めっちゃ可愛いですね。
Since it's clear, you can see what's inside, which is really cute.
推し活に向いているかな、と思っております。
I think it's quite suitable for 'oshi-katsu' (fan activities).
ぜひ手に入れてね。
Please make sure to get one.
はい、そしてお次は、こちら。スマホショルダーストラップ！
Alright, and next up is this: the Smartphone Shoulder Strap!
可愛いビーズがついてます。
It comes with cute beads.
いっぱい可愛いのついててね、色も可愛くて、めっちゃおしゃれで実用的となってます。
It's got lots of cute things on it, the color is lovely, and it's very stylish and practical.
いや、これつけてね、たくさんお出かけしてほしいですね、みんな。
I really want everyone to go out a lot while wearing this.
これ首から下げてね。いや、ぜひよろしくお願いします。
Please hang this around your neck. I'm counting on you.
そしてまだあります。次はこちら。シオンとおそろい刺繍Tシャツ！
And there's more. Next is this: Matching Embroidered T-shirt with Shion!
いやね、みんなね、ゲーミング衣装のTシャツが欲しいって、新衣装出した時にいっぱい言ってもらったので、
When I debuted my new outfit, so many people said they wanted a T-shirt of the gaming outfit,
なんと今回ね、刺繍で再現しちゃいました。
so this time, we've actually recreated it with embroidery.
フル刺繍になってます、これね。あの、プリントじゃなくて。
It's fully embroidered, you know. Not just a print.
え、だから、めっちゃクオリティ高いです。
Because of that, the quality is incredibly high.
あの、おしゃれすぎ、本当に。着てておしゃれすぎる。
It's just too stylish, seriously. It looks so good when you wear it.
シオンもこれたくさん着ます。買います、自分で。
I'm going to wear this a lot too. I'll buy one myself.
ぜひ手にとって、確かめてみてください。
Please get one and see for yourself.
いや、めっちゃ本当にクオリティめっちゃ高いから。
No, really, the quality is honestly super high.
もう、絶対手に入れてほしい。本当にTシャツ。ぜひお願いします。
I absolutely want you to have one. It's a great T-shirt. Please, check it out.
そして最後ですね。シチュエーションボイスとなっております。
And finally, we have the Situation Voice.
いや、あの、絶対手に入れてほしいってたくさん言ったけどね、全部手に入れてほしいからね。
Well, I've said "I absolutely want you to get this" a lot, but I really want you to get everything.
はい、そして最後は、フルセットの紹介です。
Alright, and finally, here's the Full Set introduction.
今回、フルセットを購入してくれた人に、数量限定で直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドがついてきます。
For those who purchase the full set, you'll get a hand-signed instax-style bromide in limited quantities.
数量限定です。ごめんなさい。
It's a limited quantity. I'm sorry.
え、でも、みんなのためにサイン頑張る、あの、よかったらお手にとってもらえたらなと思っております。
But I'll work hard on the signatures for everyone, so I hope you'll consider getting one.
数量限定です。ごめんなさい。
It's limited. I'm sorry.
さらにフルセット購入特典がもう一つあります。
Furthermore, there's another bonus for the full set purchase.
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEで使用できるカードが一枚付きます。
It includes one card that can be used in the hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME.
特典につくのは推しをアピールできるキーカード、推しホロメンカードです。
The bonus card is a "Key Card" that lets you show off your oshi, an "Oshi Holomen Card".
カードは日本語版のみとなりますので、ご了承ください。
Please note that the card will only be available in Japanese.
はい、というわけでここまで告知してきましたが、誕生日記念グッズは配信終了後に販売開始されます。
So, I've made all the announcements, and the birthday merch will go on sale after the stream ends.
概要欄にURLがあるのと、シオンのTwitterを見て確認してもらえたらなと思います。
There's a URL in the description box, and you can also check my Twitter for more details.
よろしくお願いします。数量限定だからね。
Thank you! Remember, it's a limited quantity.
そろそろ終わりの時間が来てしまいますが、
It's almost time to end the stream, but...
このあと、オリ曲MVの公開と、メン限でミニライブをやるので、よかったら遊びに来てください。
after this, an MV for my original song will premiere, and I'll be doing a mini-live on my membership channel, so please come over!
お願いします。待ってます。
Please do. I'll be waiting for you.
それでは、みんな今日は最後までありがとうございました。
Well then, thank you all for staying until the end today.
素敵な誕生日でした。
It was a wonderful birthday.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
重大告知あり！！
Major Announcement!!
紫咲シオン Birthday アニソン Live
Murasaki Shion Birthday Anisong Live